邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural.
萨姆
Sammy.
尽快把你弟弟带出屋去 快
Take your brother outside as fast as you can Go.
爸爸出去猎鬼了
Dad's on a hunting trip.
而且已经好几天没回家了
And he hasn't been home in a few days.
这是爸爸的笔记
This is Dad's book.
我认为他希望我们继续他的工作
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
猎杀恶鬼 拯救人们
You know, saving people, hunting things.
家族事业
The family business.
我要找到爸爸
I gotta find Dad.
这才是我最想做的事
It's the only thing I can think about.
（理查德 德克萨斯州 两个月前）
我说 还有多远？这儿真冷
Come on, man, is it much further? I'm cold.
应该就在附近了
Should be just up here.
哦
Whoa.
我们到了
Here we go.
你究竟是怎么找到这个地方的 瑟斯顿？
How did you find this place anyway, Thurston?
我表妹告诉我的
My cousin told me about it.
我是绝对不会进去的
Oh, I am so not going in there.
胆小鬼
Wusses.
我们好不容易过来一趟 至少也得进去看一下
We came all the way here, might as well check it out.
好吧 就逛一下然后马上回车上去
Let's just hurry this up and get back to the car.
这里实在很冷
It's freaking cold out here.
你想握着我的手吗？
Want me to hold your hand?
有其他部位也想交给我吗？
Are there any other parts I can hold?
哦 算了吧 你想得美
Ew. Shut up, you loser.
好了 来吧
Well, come on.
我有什么问题？
What?
老天
No way.
这都是些什么东西？
Look at all this stuff.
来吧 走这边
Come on. It's this way.
他们说它们徘徊在地窖里
They say that it lives in the root cellar.
专门攻击女孩子
Goes after girls. Always girls.
把她们吊死在房椽上
It just strings them up.
他们说？他们是指谁？你是从哪知道这些鬼东西？
"They say"? Who's "they"?Where did you hear this crap?
我说了 我表妹告诉我的
l told you, my cousin.
那么她从哪里听到的？
And where did she hear it?
我不知道 就是知道了呗
I don't know. She just heard it.
算了 把手电给我
Whatever. Give me that thing.
哦 看吧 邪恶的地窖
oh, look, it's the evil root cellar.
保存罐头的地方 里面总是蔬菜之类的东西
No, where Satan cans all his vegetables.
不如你们自己下来看看这里
Well, get your candy asses down here and see for yourselves.
不过是个普通的地下室
It's just a basement full.
摆着些瓶瓶罐罐 显然是某个废农场的地窖
of skank-filled jars in some crap farmhouse.
我没见到什么恐怖的东西
I don't see anything scary.
伙计们
Do you?
怎么了？
What?
你们看到什么了？
What? What is it?
《邪恶力量》
（35号州际公路 现在）
起因不明的火灾带走了我的宝贝
A fire of unknown origin took my baby away.
哈啊 很有趣
Ha-ha. Very funny.
抱歉
Sorry.
我只是想把你打扮得更像你自己
Not a lot of scenery here in east Texas. Kind of gotta make your own.
拜托 我们都不是小孩子了
Man, we're not kids anymore, Dean.
我们不能再玩那些事了
We're not gonna start that crap up again.
哪些事？
Start what up?
恶作剧 那总是很愚蠢 而且每次都一发不可收拾
That prank stuff.It's stupid and it always escalates.
哦 你有什么问题 萨姆
What's the matter, Sammy?
还怕我会把只小水獭放进你的洗发水里 嗯？
You afraid you're gonna get a little Nair in your shampoo again, huh?
行啊 这次可是你要玩的 别忘了
All right. Just remember, you started it.
哦 尽管放马过来 伙计
Bring it on, baldy.
我们这是在哪？
Where are we, anyway?
离理查德森还有两小时车程
Few hours outside of Richardson.
再给我说说那事
Give me the lowdown again.
一群孩子去了当地一幢闹鬼的屋子
kids go poking around this local haunted house.
- 闹什么鬼？- 显然是个十分凶恶的鬼魂
- Haunted by what? - Apparently, a pretty misogynistic spirit.
传说它袭击女孩 并把她们吊上房椽
Legend goes, it takes girlsand strings them up in the rafters.
无论如何 这群孩子看到一个女孩吊死在地窖里
These kids see this dead girlhanging in the cellar.
- 有人认出受害者了吗？- 问题就在这 当警察到达的时候
- Anybody ID the corpse? - Well, that's the thing.
当警察到达那里 尸体不见了
By the time the cops got there, the body was gone.
所以警察认为那些孩子耍了他们
Cops are saying the kids were yanking chains.
也许事实如此
Maybe the cops are right.
也许 但我读了那些孩子的第一手陈述
Maybe, but I read a couple of the kids' firsthand accounts.
- 描述得很真切 - 你在哪读到的？
- They seem sincere. - Where did you read these accounts?
我知道我们会经过德州
I knew we'd be passing through Texas…
所以昨天晚上 我浏览了当地的灵异事件网站
so last night, I surfed some local paranormal websites.
- 找到了这么一个网站 - 是什么？
- And I found one. - And what's it called?
Hellhoundslair.com（此网站真实存在）
Hellhoundslair.com.
让我猜猜 母亲的地窖不停有水流出？
Let me guess.Streaming live out of Mom's basement.
- 差不多 - 可能吧
- Yeah, probably. - Yeah.
事实上 那些经营网站的人 即使被鬼咬了
Most of those websites wouldn't know…
也不明白究竟发生了什么
a ghost if it bit them in the "persqueeter."
我说 就这么让爸爸走了 显然是一个错误
Look, we let Dad take off, which was a mistake, by the way.
现在我们根本不知道他在哪里
Now we don't know where he is.
所以我们需要找些事做
Meantime, we gotta find something to hunt.
去查一下这件事显然没有害处
No harm checking this out.
好吧 那我们去哪找那些孩子？
All right, so where do we find these kids?
在这种城市里年青人通常会去的地方
Same place you always find kids in a town like this.
那是我生平见到的最可怕的事 我发誓
It was the scariest thing I ever saw, I swear to God.
我一踏进那里 就看到墙壁上刷的符号 黑色的
From the moment we walked in.The walls were painted black.
- 红色的 - 我觉得那是血
- Red. - I think it was blood.
- 可怕的符号 - 十字型
- All these freaky symbols. - Crosses and stars, and…
- 星型 - 五角星
- Pentagons. - Pentecostals.
总之 我一直提心吊胆
Whatever, I had my eyes closed.
但我可以绝对保证 无论别人说什么
I can tell you this much No matter what anybody says-
- 那个可怜的女孩 - 黑衣服
- That poor girl. - With the black…
- 绿眼睛 - 红头发 就吊在那里
- Blonde. - Red hair, just hanging there.
- 在半空中 - 一动不动
- Kicking. - Without even moving.
- 那是真的 - 百分百真实
- She was real. - It's 100 percent.
她还挺漂亮
And kind of hot.
- 当然 除了死亡那一部分 - 好吧
- Well, you know, in a dead sort of way. - Okay.
你们怎么找到那个地方的？
And how did you find out about this place, anyway?
- 克雷格 - 克雷格带我们去的
- Craig. - Craig took us.
嗨 能为你们效劳吗？
Fellas. Help you with anything?
- 你是克雷格·瑟斯顿？- 正是
- Yeah, are you Craig Thurston? - I am.
我们是「达拉斯晨报」的记者
We're reporters with The Dallas Morning News.
- 我是迪恩 这位是萨姆 - 没门
- l'm Dean, this is Sam. - No way.
真巧 我也是个写手 为学校的文学杂志写文章
Yeah, l'm a writer too.I write for my school's lit. magazine.
听起来不错
Well, good for you, Morrissey.
我们正在写一篇关于本地灵异事件的文章
Um, we're doing an article on local hauntings.
我听说你知道一起
Rumor has it you might know about one.
- 你是说鬼屋？- 就是那个
- You mean the Hell House? - That's the one.
我不知道该从何说起
I didn't think there was anything to the story.
给我们说说那个故事
Why don't you tell us the story.
好吧 假设 在30年代
Well, supposedly, back in the '30s…
一个叫默德凯·默多克农场主
this farmer, Mordechai Murdock,
和他的六个女儿住在那里
he used to live in the house with his six daughters.
在经济大萧条时期 他的作物没有收成
It was during the Depression, his crops were failing…
他没钱养活自己的女儿
he didn't have enough money to feed his children.
我猜事情就这样发生了
So I guess that's when he went off the deep end.
怎么发生的？
How?
我猜 他认为让女儿们痛快地死去
Well, he figured it was best if his girls died quick…
比慢慢饿死要强
rather than starve to death.
所以他攻击她们
So he attacked them.
她们尖叫 企求他停止 但他没有
And they screamed, begged for him to stop…
他把她们一个一个吊死
but he just strung them up, one after another.
当一切都结束 他最后上吊自杀
And then when it was all finished, he turned around and hung himself.
有人说从此以后那些鬼魂就被困在那幢房子了
Now they say that his spirit is trapped in the house forever…
吊死任何一个走进去的女孩
stringing up any other girl that goes inside.
你从哪听说这些的？
And where did you hear all this?
我的表妹戴娜告诉我的 我不知道她从哪听来的
My cousin Dana told me.I don't know where she heard it from.
说实话 我从没相信过那回事
You gotta realize, I didn't believe this for a second.
但现在你信了
But now you do.
我不知道 我不明白那是什么
I don't know what the hell to think, man.
行了 这些话我对警察也是这么说的
You guys, l'll tell you exactly what I told the police, okay?
那个女孩是真的 她死了 这不是什么恶作剧
That girl was real, and she was dead.This was not a prank.
我发誓我再也不想接近那幢房子了
I swear to God, I don't wanna go anywhere near that house…
永远不
ever again, okay?
多谢
Thanks.
- 我得说 我相信那个孩子 - 很多事有待调查
- Can't say I blame the kid. - Yeah, so much for curb appeal.
有线索吗？
You got something?
- 没有 EMF不能用 - 怎么会？
- Yeah, but the EMF's no good. - Why?
我猜是那些东西干扰了信号 这是所有的读数
I think that thing's still got a little juice in it. It's screwing with all the readings.
是啊 很有可能
Yeah, that would do it.
来吧 我们进去
Come on, let's go.
看来老默多克生前是个恶魔崇拜者
Looks like old man Murdock was a bit of a tagger during his time.
死后也是
And after his time too.
倒十字被用于恶魔崇拜已经有几世纪了
The reverse cross has been used by Satanists for centuries…
但硫磺印记直到
but this Sigil of Sulfur didn't show up.
60年代才首次在旧金山出现
in San Francisco until the '60s.
难怪你总是不得安宁
That's exactly why you never get laid.
这个呢 你有见过吗？
Hey, what about this one?You seen this one before?
没有
No.
我见过
I have.
但想不起在哪了
Somewhere.
这是喷漆
It's paint.
而且还是新喷的
Seems pretty fresh too.
我不太清楚 萨姆
I don't know, Sam.
虽然我俩从不相信官方的结论
I mean, I hate to agree with authority figures of any kind…
但我认为这次他们可能是对的
but the cops might be right about this one.
可能
Yeah, maybe.
老天 原来是两个人
Cut. Just a couple of humans.
你们来这里干吗？
What are you guys doing here?
你们才是来这里干吗？
What the hell are you doing here?
我们属于这里 我们是职业的
We belong here. We're professionals.
- 职业干什么的？- 灵异事件调查者
- Professional what? - Paranormal investigators.
这个 好好看看 伙计们
There you go. Take a look at that, boys.
不是真的吧
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
- 艾德·瑟德莫尔和哈利·斯潘格勒。-
Ed Zeddmore and Harry Spangler.
Hellhoundslair.com 那网站是你们的？
Hellhoundslair.com. You guys run that website?
- 是啊 - 喔 耶 我们可是那的忠实粉丝
- Yeah. - Oh, yeah, yeah. We're huge fans.
我知道你们是干吗的
And we know who you guys are too.
- 是吗 - 业余人员
- Oh, yeah? - Amateurs.
为了单纯的刺激 搜寻鬼魂 没错
Looking for ghosts and cheap thrills. Yeah.
所以 如果你们不介意的话
So if you guys don't mind…
我们正要开始严肃的科学调查
we're trying to conduct a seriousscientific investigation here.
那你们发现什么了吗？
Yeah? What do you got so far?
哈利 不如你和他们说说EMF？
Harry, why don't you tell them about EMF?
EMF？
EMF?
电磁场探测器
Electromagnetic field.
鬼怪会引起能量的异常波动
Spectral entities can cause energy fluctuations…
这种信号可以用EMF探测到
that can be read with an EMF detector…
应该就是这附近的波段
like this bad boy right here.
喔 喔
Whoa. Whoa.
- 那是2.8毫克 - 二点八
- That's 2.8 MG. - Two point eight.
在这里很热
It's hot in here.
你们以前有见过真实的鬼魂吗？
Huh. So have you guys ever really seen a ghost before, or…?
有一次
Once. We were…
我们在调查一幢旧房子
We were investigating this old house…
然后我们看到一只花瓶从桌上摔了下来
and we saw a vase fall right off the table.
- 自己摔下来的 - 我们… 也许… 没有亲眼见到
- By itself. - We didn't actually see it…
但我们听到了 一旦经历过那种事情
but we heard it, and something like that…
- 你的一生就会改变 - 是啊
- …it changes you. - Yeah.
我想我能理解
I think I get the picture.
我看我们俩该走了 让他们继续工作吧
We should go, let them get back to work.
是啊 你们是该走了 萨姆
- Yeah, you should. - Sam.
好 工作
Yeah, work.
抱歉 我们通常用笑声开始工作
I'm sorry. That pot we smoked gave me the giggles.
（科林郡公共图书馆）
- 嗨 - 嗨 查到什么了？
- Hey. - Hey. What do you got?
我没查到有默德凯
I couldn't find a Mordechai…
但我确实找到一个叫莫得·默多克的人
but I did turn up a Martin Murdockwho.
30年代住在那幢房子里
lived in that house in the '30s.
他的确有孩子 但只有两个 都是男孩
He did have children, but only two of them, both boys.
而且也没有记录显示他杀害了他们
And there's no record he ever killed anyone.
你查到什么？
What about you?
虽然那些孩子给出了女孩的详细外貌描述
Kids didn't give a clear description of that girl.
但我去警察局查的时候
I did hit up the police station.
没有发现相符的失踪人口报告
No matching missing persons.
好像这个女孩从来不曾存在一样
It's like she never existed.
行了 Sam 我们查过了 这整件事是个恶作剧
Dude, come on. We did our digging.This one's a bust.
那些孩子捏造了所有故事
For all we know, those Hellhound boys made up the whole thing.
- 好吧 - 我说不如我们找个小酒吧
- Yeah, all right. - I say we find ourselves a bar…
吃点喝点 让传说见鬼去吧
and some beers and leave the legend to the locals.
这到底…
What the…?
这就是你的把戏？
That's all you got? It's weak.
真够逊的
That is bush league.
就是这了
This is it.
- 有去无回的地方 - 为什么我非得去那？
- The point of no return. - Why do I have to go in there?
吉尔因为你选择冒险而不是说真话
Because, Jill, you chose dare instead of truth.
所以要么你去莫迪凯的地窖里
You either have to grab a jar from Mordechai's cellar…
拿个罐头回来 或者
and bring it back, or…
或者你和我约会
Or you can make out with me.
算了 我宁愿去鬼屋一趟
I'll take the homicidal ghost, thanks.
- 你相信里面会死人吗？- 我不知道
- Would you ever take that dare? - Hell, no.
有人吗？
Hello?
这里有人吗？
Is anybody there?
发生什么了？
Hold on one second, Mr. Goodwin.
发生看什么事
What happened?
警察说那个女孩在里面上吊
Cops say that poor girl hung herself in the house.
- 自杀？- 是啊
- Suicide? - Yeah.
她是个成绩全A的优秀学生 前途无量
And she was a straight-A student with a full ride to UT too.
这说不通
It just don't make sense.
你觉得呢？
What do you think?
也许我们忽略了一些东西
I think maybe we missed something.
我猜警察们不想让任何人进入那幢房子
The cops don't want any more kids screwing around in there.
但我们还是得进去
Yeah, but we still gotta get in there.
真不敢相信
I don't believe it.
我有主意了
I got an idea.
「你会找谁？」
Who you gonna call?
嗨 你们
Hey, you.
跑
Run.
- 快 - 回来
- Come on. - Get back here.
- 停下 - 快跑 不要离开我
- Stop. - Come on, don't leave me here.
我肯定见过这个符号 但就是想不起来 真要命
Where have I seen that symbol? It's killing me.
快点 我们没多少时间
Come on. We don't have much time.
嗨 萨姆 我猜你愿意尝尝这个
Hey, Sam, I dare you to take a swig of this.
我会这样做的？
What the hell would I do that for?
这是你喜欢的牌子
I double dare you.
我恨老鼠
I hate rats.
- 你宁愿是个鬼魂？- 没错
- You'd rather it was a ghost? - Yes.
这是什么鬼魂 盐块竟然不起作用
What kind of spirit is immune to rock salt?
我不知道
I don't know.
快走 快 快
Come on, come on, come on.
快离开这
Go. Get out of here.
- 也许我们该离开 - 不
- Maybe we should just go. - No.
想想约翰·爱德华会离开吗？
Would John Edward go?
我们甩掉了警察
No, we've lost the cops.
现在让我们静下心来 全力工作
Let's find our center and get some work done.
好吗？好吧 好吧
Okay? All right, okay.
- 那该死的鬼魂出乎我的意料 - 快跑
- Get that damn thing out of my face. - Go, go, go.
亲爱的上帝… 是个环。-
Sweet Lord…Of the Rings.
快跑 快 快
Run. Go, go, go.
那个人刚才还…
Look, there's a-Look.There's a man over there.
- 他去哪里了？- 好了 小伙子们 跟我们走
- I saw… Where'd he go? - Boys. Come on.
该死 这到底是什么符号
What the hell is this symbol?
真是烦死我了
It's bugging the hell out of me.
整个调查过程真是要命
This whole damn job's bugging me.
不是说默德凯只攻击女孩子嘛
I thought the legend said that Mordechai only goes after chicks.
- 这是 - 没错
- lt does. - All right.
那他攻击你还情有可原 但为什么也攻击我呢？
That explains why he went after you.But why me?
真好笑
Hilarious.
传说他是上吊自杀的 但你看到他那断裂的手腕了吗？
Legend also says he hung himself.But you see those slit wrists?
- 恩 - 怎么回事？
- Yeah. - What's up with that?
还有斧子
And the ax too?
鬼魂通常是有固定行事模式的 不是吗？
Ghosts are usually pretty strict, right?
每次应该都是一样的…
Following the same patterns over and over.
- 为什么这个的行为模式会不断改变 - 没错
- But this mook keeps changing.|- Exactly.
我说 故事是…
I'm telling you, the way the story goes…
等一下
Wait a minute.
怎么了？
What?
有人在网上发了个新贴 听听这段
Someone added a new posting to the Hellhound site. Listen to this:
他们说莫德凯是个拿着斧子砍人的恶魔崇拜者
"They say Mordechai Murdock was really a Satanist…
直到他的手腕断了为止
who chopped up his victims with an ax before slitting his own wrists.
因此他被永远禁锢在那所房子里
Now he's imprisoned in the house for eternity."
这究竟是怎么回事？
Where the hell is this going?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我刚知道这一切是从哪开始的
But I think I might havejust figured out where it all started.
嗨 克雷格
Hey, Craig.
还记得我们吗？
Remember us?
伙计 我真的没什么心情回答你们的问题
Guys, l'm really not in the mood to answer any more of your questions.
哦 没事 我们买完东西就走
Oh, don't worry. Don't worry. We're just here to buy an album, that's all.
你看 我实在想不出那个符号代表什么
You know, I couldn't figure out what that symbol was.
后来我突然发现 其实那个符号一点意义也没有
And then I realized it doesn't mean anything.
那不过是Blue Oyster Cult（老牌摇滚乐队）的标志
It's the logo for Blue yster Cult.
告诉我克雷格 你是喜欢BOC
Tell me, Craig. You into BOC?
还是想把人们吓得屁滚尿流？
Or just scaring the hell out of people?
我想你告诉我那幢房子的事
Now, why don't you tell us about that house.
这次不要说没谱的谎话了
Without lying through your ass this time.
好吧
All right.
我的表妹戴娜正好放假从TCU回来
My cousin Dana was on break from TCU.
我猜我们只是有点无聊 想找些事做
I guess we were just bored, looking for something to do.
正好我知道那有个废弃的农场
So I showed her this abandoned dump I found.
我想如果把那里布置成好像闹鬼的样子 一定很有趣
We thought it'd be funny if we made it look like it was haunted.
于是我们在墙上画了些符号
So we painted symbols on the walls.
有些来自唱片
Some from some albums.
有些来自戴娜的意识形态课本
Some from some of Dana's theology textbooks.
后来我们发现有个默多克曾住在那里
Then we found out this guy, Murdock, used to live there…
所以就顺势编了那个故事
so we made up some story to go along with that.
然后就一传十 十传百
So they told people who told other people.
还有两个人把这些搬上了那个愚蠢的网站
And then these two guys put it on their stupid website.
所有的一下子
Everything just…
就变成真的了
took on a life of its own.
我最初只是觉得好玩
I mean, I thought it was funny at first, but…
但现在 我真不知道该怎么承受这种结果
Now that girl's dead.
这不过是个玩笑
It was just a joke.
那些传说都是假的 全是我们自编自导自演
You know, I mean, none of it was real. We made the whole thing up.
我发誓
I swear.
好吧
All right.
如果这些都不是真的 那怎么解释莫德凯？
If none of it was real, how the hell do you explain Mordechai?
我回来了
Hey, I'm back.
嗨 你去哪了？
Hey, where were you?
出去了一会儿
Oh, I went out.
我想了个能够解释莫德凯存在的理论
So I think I might have a theory about what's going on.
- 是什么？- 说不定莫德凯是个Tulpa
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah, what if Mordechai is a tulpa?
- Tulpa？- 对 一种源自西藏的思想
- Tulpa? - Yeah, a Tibetan Thought-form.
我知道Tulpa是什么
Yeah, no, I know what a tulpa is.
你还是穿上衣服吧
Hey, why don't you get dressed.I wanna go grab something to eat.
- 我要用一下洗手间 - 谢谢
- There you go, gents. - Thank you.
嗨 你怎么了？
Dude, what's your problem?
- 没事 - 我很好
- Nothing. l'm fine. - Yeah?
哦
Yeah.
好吧 继续说 关于Tulpa
All right, so keep going.What about these tulpas?
50年代的时候 在西藏有一次意外
Okay, so there was this incident in Tibet in 1915.
一群僧侣在脑海里想象假人
Group of monks visualize a golem in their heads.
因为他们冥想得太厉害 所以那东西真的变活了
They meditate on it so hard, they bring the thing to life.
- 就这么凭空被创造了出来 - 所以？
- Out of thin air. - So?
那不过是20个僧侣
That was 20 monks.
想象一下千万个网民能创造出什么？
Imagine what 10, 000 web surfers could do.
我想说的是 克雷格编了这个故事
I mean, Craig starts the story about Mordechai…
然后故事上了网络
then it spreads, goes online.
现在成千上万的人都确信这个混蛋的存在
Now countless people believe in the bastard.
你想告诉我
Wait. You're trying to tell me…
就因为人们相信莫德凯存在 所以他存在？
that just because people believe in Mordechai, he's real?
我不知道 可能吧
I don't know. Maybe.
人们也相信圣诞老人 我怎么从没在圣诞节看到过他？
People believe in Santa Claus. How come I'm not hooked up every Christmas?
第一 你不是什么好人 第二 你看这个
Because you're a bad person.And because of this:
那是西藏的灵魂印记
That's a Tibetan spirit sigil.
就画在墙上
On the wall of the house.
Craig说他们照着意识形态的课本画的
Craig said they were painting from a textbook.
我猜他们甚至不知道那些符号的意义
I bet they painted this not even knowing what it was.
这个印记已经沿用了几世纪了
That sigil has been used for centuries.
它像放大镜一样聚集冥想思维的力量
Concentrating meditative thoughts like a magnifying glass.
所以上Hellhoundslair的人
People are on the Hellhound's website…
整天盯着这个印记 想着莫德凯的事
staring at the symbol, thinking about Mordechai…
我不太清楚 但很可能会创造出莫德凯
I mean, I don't know, but it might be enough to bring aatulpa to life.
那同时解释了为什么莫德凯的行为模式会改变
It would explain why he keeps changing.
没错 当传说改变 人们的想法也会改变
Right. As the legend changes, people think different things…
所以莫德凯也随之改变
so Mordechai himself changes.
就像电话游戏
Like a game of Telephone.
而且那也解释了为什么盐块对它不起作用
Would also explain why rock salt didn't work.
因为那不是传统意义上的鬼魂
Because he's not a traditional spirit, per se.
- 没错 - 那么我们把印记擦掉
- Yeah. - Okay. So why don't we just…
让故事下网
get this spirit-sigil thingy off the wall and the website.
事实上 没有那么简单
Well, it's not that simple.
一旦Tulpa被创造出来 它们就能独立存在
You see, once tulpas are created, they take on a life of their own.
太好了 如果它是一种思维形式的实体
Great. All right, so if he really is a Thought-form…
我们怎么能消灭一种思想？
how the hell are we supposed to kill an idea?
有这两个人在帮倒忙 我想这件事很不容易做
Well, it's not gonna be easy with these guys helping us.
看看他们网站的更新
Check out their home page.
自从他们上载了这段影像
Since they posted the video…
网站的点击率在一天内增加了数倍
the number of hits have quadrupled in the last day alone.
嗯 我有主意了 来吧
I got an idea. Come on.
- 我们去哪儿？- 我们得找个复印店
- Where we going? - We need to find a copy store.
伙计 我觉得我对刚才用的肥皂还是其他什么东西过敏
Man. I think l'm allergic to our soap or something.
是你搞的鬼？
You did this?
- 你真是个可恶的混蛋 - 是吗
- You're a frigging jerk. - Oh, yeah.
不 不 不 不
No, no.
你不要想了 我不会回到那里去的
No, forget it.I'm not going back in there again.
哈利你看着我 看着我的眼睛
Harry, look at me. Right here. Okay?
你是个猎魔者
You're a ghost hunter. Okay?
我知道 但我从没真正见过鬼
I know but, Ed, I've never actually seen a real ghost before.
真正的鬼可是会移形换影的
An apparition.This stuff here…
但就这一次冒险就能带给我们名望 金钱 女人
this is our ticket to the big time.Fame, money, sex.
像女孩 好吧 勇敢点
With girls. Okay? Be brave.
行了巴菲会怎么做？
Okay, W.W.B.D.
- 巴菲会怎么做 - 巴菲会怎么做
- What would Buffy do? Huh? - What would Buffy do?
但她比我强壮多了
I know, but, Ed, she's stronger than me.
这没关系
It's okay.
是谁？快出来
Who is it?Come on out here.
我们有消息给你们
We hear you in there.
真是
It's them.
看看
Oh, look at that.
没有包装的动作明星 真是惊人
Action figures in their original packaging.What a shock.
伙计们 我们要谈谈
Guys, we need to talk.
我们现在正忙着
Yeah, sorry, guys, we're a little bit busy right now.
我们很快就能说完 我们想要你们关掉网站
Well, we'll make it quick.We need you to shut down your website.
显然 这两位昨晚受惊了
These guys get us busted last night.We spend the night in a cell.
我希望你们说出昨晚的经历 我可以给你们这个机会
I had to pee in front of people.And I get stage fright.
- 我们为什么要相信你们？- 听着 伙计
- Why should we trust you guys? - Look, guys…
我们都知道昨晚屋里有什么
we all know what we saw.What's in the house.
而因为你们的网站
Thanks to your website…
现在成千上万的人都知道这个莫德凯了
there are thousands of people hearing about Mordechai.
也就意味着 会不断有人跑去那
Means people are gonna keep showing up at Hell House…
遇到Mordecai本人 会有人因此受伤
running into him, could get hurt.
- 没错 - 也许他们说的对
- Yeah. - Maybe he's got a point.
- 不 - 不
- No. - No.
对 不 我们有义务让公众知道真相
Okay, we have an obligation to our fans, to the truth.
而我没有义务让双方…
I have an obligation to kick your asses.
迪恩 算了 这些家伙
Dean. Hey, just forget it, all right? These guys…
这两个人只想自己干
You could bitch-slap them.
即使我告诉他们那些关于莫德凯的事情…
I could probably even tell them that thing about Mordechai.
他们还是不会帮我们的
But they're still not gonna help us.
- 所以我们还是走吧 - 你说的对
- Let's just go. - Yeah, you're right.
- 你怎么说 - 嗨 等等
- What'd you say about…? - No. Wait.
- 等一下 - 在这里等一下
- Wait, wait. - Hold on a second here.
关于莫德凯的什么事？
What thing about Mordechai, you guys?
- 萨姆 - 不要告诉他们 如果他们愿意把网站关掉
- Don't tell them. - If they agree to shut the website down…
他们不会的 你自己也说了
They're not. Said so yourself.
不要听他的 我们会关掉的
No, wait, wait.Don't listen to him, okay? We'll do it.
我们把网站关掉
We'll do it.
这是秘密萨姆
It's a secret, Sam.
好吧 这是个大新闻 很不容易搞到
Look, it is a pretty big deal.And it wasn't easy to dig up.
所以除非你们保证会把一切都结束
So only if we have your word you'll shut everything down.
绝对会
Totally.
好吧
All right.
这是30年代的一份死亡证明
It's a death certificate from the '30s.
我们从图书馆得到的
We got it at the library.
根据上面说的
According to the coroner…
莫德凯的真正死因是自制子弹的枪击
the actual cause of death was a self-inflicted gunshot wound.
没错 他没有上吊或砍死自己
He didn't hang or cut himself.
他是吞枪自杀的？没错 用把。-45口径的手枪
He shot himself?Yep. With a.45 pistol.
- 直到今天他仍然害怕这种手枪 - 如果你用A45射杀他
- They say he's terrified of them. - lf you shoot him with a.45…
事实上 如果用把。-45口径的手枪 装上自制的熟铁子弹射击他
loaded with these special wrought-iron rounds…
就能杀死这个混蛋
you'd kill the son of a bitch.
哈利 慢点 周末有事做了
Harry. Slow your roll, buddy.
他们知道我们会很兴奋。-
They're gonna know we're excited.
你要是再拉一下那玩意儿 我就杀了你
If you pull that string one more time, I'm gonna kill you.
行了 老弟 你该多笑笑
Come on, man.You need more laughter in your life.
你一直过于紧张了
You know, you're way too tense.
他们发表了吗？
They post it yet?
我们得到可靠消息 手枪能杀死莫德凯· 默多克
"We've learned from reputable sources…
不错 我们要等多久？
that Mordechai Murdock has a fatal fear of firearms."
直到新的故事传开
All right. How long do we wait?
传说改变为止
Long enough for the new story to spread and the legend to change.
我已经想好晚上做什么了 爱尔兰的足球赛
I figure by nightfall, iron rounds will work on the sucker.
干
Sweet.
是你干的？
You didn't.
是我干的
Oh. I did.
我不骗你 我听到声音了
I'm telling you, I heard something.
从那边传过来的
Coming from over there.
听
See?
又来了
There it is again.
这是什么东西？
What is that?
瞧你做的好事
What the…?
我手上几乎都没皮了
I barely have any skin left on my palm.
早知今日 何必当初
I aingt touching that line with a 10-foot pole.
你觉得莫德凯在家吗？
Well, you think old Mordechai's home?
我不知道
I don't know.
我也不知道
Me neither.
你们在干吗？找死吗？
You trying to get yourself killed?
我们不过想拍一段预定了的视频
We're trying to get a book-and-movie deal.
哦 上帝
Oh, crap.
伙计们 你们不想先进那扇门吗？
Uh, guys, you wanna…You wanna go open that door for us?
为什么你不先进去？
Why don't you?
他消失了 消失了
Oh, God, he's gone. He's gone.
- 你得到了吗？- 得到了
- Did you get him? - Yeah, they got him.
我说摄像机 你拍下来了没？
No, on camera.Did you get him on camera?
- 我看 - 让我看看 让我看看
- Well, l… - Let me see it. Let me see it.
看
Hey.
你们有没有把我们给的文章发到网上？
Didn't you post that B.S. story we gave you?
- 当然有 - 但后来服务器垮了
- Of course. - Then our server crashed.
- 这么说 - 等于没发咯？
- Yeah. - So it didn't take?
所以这些枪根本不管用
So these These guns don't work?
是啊
Yeah.
真太好了
Great. Sam, any ideas?
- 萨姆 有主意吗？- 有
- We are getting out of here. - Yeah.
我们离开这 来吧 快点
Come on, Ed.
好
Yeah.
快跑 快跑
Okay. Let's go, let's go.
母亲 玛丽和约瑟夫…
Mother, Mary and Joseph…
上帝的力量使你…
The power of Christ compels you…
哟 来抓我 你这混蛋
Come and get it, you ugly son of a bitch.
离开这 快点
Get out of here. Now.
我们离开这里
We're out of here.
迪恩
Dean.
快走 快
Go, go.
快点走
Come on.
听着 莫德凯不那离开房子 我们能够杀死他
Mordechai can't leave the house, we can't kill him…
这样做应该行
We improvise.
焚毁？
That's your solution?
你想把这里夷为平地？
Burn the whole damn place to the ground?
这样就没人会再进去了
No one will go in anymore.
如果房子不存在了 莫德凯也就不存在了
I mean, Mordechai can't haunt a house if there's no house to haunt.
这虽然极端 但有效
It's fast and dirty, but it works.
万一传说又改变了 让莫德凯能够离开房子呢？
What if the legend changes and Mordechai is allowed to leave?
那我们就得再回来一趟了
Well, then we'll just have to come back.
不敢相信
Kind of makes you wonder.
在所有我们猎杀的东西里
Of all the things we hunted…
有多少只是因为人们相信才存在的
how many existed just because people believed in them?
莫德凯一事确实物有所值
I was thinking that Mordechai has a really super-high attack bonus.
伙计 我现在饿了
Dude, I got the munchies right now.
- 先生们 - 嗨 伙计
- Gentlemen. - Hey, guys.
- 她会报道吗？- 也许
- Should we tell them? - Eh, might as well.
她还要再细读一下
They're gonna read about it in the trades.
今天早上
This morning…
我们收到好莱坞一个著名制片人的电话
we got a phone call from an important Hollywood producer.
- 打错了？- 当然不是 小哥
- Oh, yeah, wrong number? - No, smart-ass.
他在网上读到了所有关于鬼屋的报道
He read all about the Hell House on our website…
然后问我们是否愿意参与他的制作团队
and wants to option the motion-picture rights.
可能会要我们写剧本
Maybe even have us write it.
- 而且还会出RPG - 什么？
- And create the RPG. - The what?
- 角色扮演游戏 - 不错
- Role-playing game. - Right.
这种行话你们是不会懂的 所以 如果不介意的话
Little lingo for you.Anywho, excuse us.
我们要上路了
We're off to La-La Land.
恭喜你们了 听起来非常不错
Well, congratulations.That sounds really great.
是啊 祝你们好运
Yeah, that's awesome. Best of luck.
哦 其实根本不关运气的事 是才能
Oh, yeah, luck. It's got nothing to do with it. It's about talent.
完全是因为我们的才能
You know, sheer, unabashed talent.
回见
Later.
希望能再见到你
See you around.
- 我需要坦白一点 - 坦白什么？
- I have a confession to make. - What's that?
是我打的电话还告诉他们我是制片人的
I was the one who called them and told them I was a producer.
我把死鱼扔在了他们的后车座上
I'm the one who put the dead fish in their back seat.
真相？
Truce?
真相 至少在几百公里内
Yeah, truce.At least for the next hundred miles.